Also, this is probably
the only time
I'll get to compete against
Anne at the exhibition.
This year will be
Anne's final chance.
It is a great honour for me.
It's her final chance.
That's right. If she
can't become a silver
sugar master this time,
then she can never become one.
How's that one coming? Can you trade
positions? All right. And look.
This place is crawling
with sugar artisans.
But wait. We need to lower
the heat now. Understood?
I don't see any female workers.
That's because women
are transgressors against God.
And sugar confections
are a sacred food.
So it's frowned upon for
women to create them. Pardon me?
Back when God made
the first man and woman,
he intended for humankind
to rule over the world.
But a woman fell
in love with the king
of the fairies and vowed
her allegiance to him instead.
Ancestor King Cedric cleansed
us of this woman's
selfish crime and set us free
from the fairies control,
building a world that better
aligned with God's wishes.
I see somebody skipped out
on the church's rest day school.
I'm sorry. Well,
it's just an old story anyway.
Regardless, throughout history,
it's been cited as the reason
why most artisans have been men.
Personally, I think it has
more to do with the physical
strain that comes with the job.
It took you a while, Hingley.
Jonas.
If only your students had communicated
the news better. Mr. Ratcliffe.
Huh? All these years,
and somehow you
haven't learned
to watch your mouth.
Ratcliffe as in Marcus Radcliffe, the
headmaster of this school.
You were the one
who didn't inform
the silver Sugar Viscount
that you had relocated.
Oh. Save it.
Just give me some work.
I'm here for silver
sugar like the rest.
Actually, you will be overseeing
the refinement
process as a whole with the help
of young Elliott Collins.
Elliott, too.
I figured he was busy
since he's serving as the head
of the page workshop.
He left in a rush,
but he's still late. Of course.
That louse is late. I'll
get started without him, then.
And you must be Anne Halford.
Yes.
This workshop is in my charge.
I'm
Marcus Radcliffe,
and that's my nephew.
I hear you've taken
good care of him.
I've also heard
that you plan to take
part in the sugar
confectionery exhibition,
but if your
work doesn't measure up,
you won't receive
any sugar apples.
I understand,
and I assure you I'll succeed.
We process silver sugar
in bulk here.
The mortars, ladles
and paddles are quite heavy.
Can you work with them as well
as a man would? Yes I can.
Willpower alone won't be enough.
Be sure
that you're not
a nuisance to these men.
Best of luck. Thank you sir.
You'd better keep
your wits about you, Jonas.
Both she and Keith
are worthy opponents.
I understand, uncle, if.
You allow this girl
to outdo you again
at this year's exhibition,
Keith will be the only
suitable candidate
as our next head master.
All right. Don't disappoint me.
Sounds like you have your
own troubles. No one asked you.
All right, then,
I'll go get to work.
Sure. Do whatever you want.
Since my uncle
obviously doesn't mind it,
I will. And hold on.
Kat, I'm joining the workers.
Just tell me what to do. Ah.
Ah, that's quite a good
look for you.
It's easier to move
around in this.
We could use more people on the
bigger cauldron. Start there. Right.
I'll go lend a hand to you.
Work in the background.
The wagons are leaving soon.
Bored? One of them.
So you can help
harvest the sugar apples.
What with him.
We've got work to do.
Let's go. After all, if you
don't work, you don't eat.
You sure got an
impressive work ethic.
See through the names.
Me through lit pod.
Hey, don't fall asleep on me.
Change out. I'm ready.
It's really hot. Stop! That's
too heavy for a woman to move.
I'll be fine.
Hey, this is a man's job.
You're in the way.
Oh, that's no place for a girl,
silly. Let me help you.
Wouldn't want you falling and
scratching up your pretty face.
Pardon? No need to thank me.
I'm happy to help women. So.
Would you care to have
tea with me sometime?
Uh. Uh, it's about time
you showed up, Elliot.
I see your eyesight
still as sharp as ever.
Silver sugar master
Elliot Collins. He's standing
in for the master
of the page workshop.
You there? You're not a sugar
artisan. What? Yes, I am.
Elliot. Why'd you bring
a non artisan in here?
Get to work already! But first
apologize for being late.
That is so rude of you.
I'll have you know.
This is the young lady of the
page workshop. What? She is.
Yes. My name is Bridget Page,
the daughter of Glen page.
And what brings you here?
She wanted to visit with me,
of course.
Oh, and she's my fiance.
Elliot. I came here
to help in the kitchen.
I do hope I am not the only
woman who's here to cook.
That's just the official reason
she wishes to cheer me on.
While I amaze all
of you with my talent.
You haven't done anything yet.
And why
are you standing around?
Oh, right.
Gentlemen.
What are those faces for? We let
anyone work who's
willing to work? Oh.
One.
I don't know.
Don't you think you could
at least give her
a job that's more ladylike?
And what would that be?
She could serve tea,
do some cleaning,
or maybe just chat with me.
Chatting with you
isn't a real job.
Besides,
that girl is a genuine artisan.
I'm not so sure that I can
believe that she's a woman.
That's an outdated way of
thinking. It's clearly impossible.
But she still refuses to give up
such absurdness.
I'm going into town.
Great. I'll come with you.
You can't.
You and I have a meeting
right now. What we do.
Kat's giving me this chance.
If I can't
do it, I won't get sugar apples.
I'll help her find
the silver sugar
so I can make my peace. Uh.
Here. Thank you. And here's
yours. I appreciate it. Oh. I'm.
Here. Can I have extra?
I'm sorry. The portions are set.
That's
all I can give.
Next worker, please.
I would like some.
How can you trust that way?
You are a girl after all.
May I have some food, please?
It's one plate per person.
It's for my friends.
I had like, enough for them too.
It's all right. Give her
what she asked for, Keith.
I'll have a serving.
Um. All right. Sure.
Something wrong? Oh, no.
Here you are. Thank you.
Let's retire then. Right. Thank you. Keith.
You're quite welcome. And shall.
He.
Huh? Huh? Yes. Oh. It's you.
I only came to see you
because my uncle made me.
He says the sugar apples from today's
harvest are in the storehouse.
So if you want them for this
year's piece,
he's giving me some.
Anyway, that's all I had to tell
you. So I'll be right back.
That's right.
If she can't become
a silver sugar master this time.
Then she can never become one.
Huh?
Now I can make silver sugar.
I'm so happy you.
Oh, shell. Aren't I heavy?
Yes. Of course.
You're a scarecrow.
That doesn't make sense.
And it's mean.
You want me with you?
I suppose it's me.
Who desires that?
Poor thing.
I can't believe that girl
forces you to work this late,
huh? Wait.
You should know. If you're not happy
with the situation you're in,
then I would be
happy to purchase you.
I would never make you
work the way that she does.
You wouldn't have to do anything. I
know you would love it.
I would give you a nice room
and plenty
of sugar confections to.
You would have
a great life with me.
So I would become a pet, huh?
I refuse your offer. Human.
Hey, you're still
skimming off the scum.
You leave too much.
The sugar tastes bad.
That's enough already. Now go
get started on the next batch.
It'll be mixed
with the stuff from the other
cauldron anyway,
so there's no point.
But if you keep lowering
the quality bit by bit,
then the final mix
is going to taste terrible.
Oh pipe down,
all the silver sugar
for this year is going
to be mass produced anyway.
No one cares whether
it's good quality.
Really nobody cares.
If that's the case,
our next year's
piece is going to
be made from inferior sugar, too.
It's everyone who
buys a confection.
Going to get such poor quality.
But what
if it's something incredibly
significant that they can
only buy once
in their entire lives?
This isn't worth getting
into a fight over, and.
It's being quiet would fix
the problem. I'd be quiet.
I won't stand for this.
Creating sugar confections.
With this kind of attitude
is wrong. What did you just say?
And I think it's time
for your break. Huh?
Calm down.
Mr. Hingley and Mr. Collins
make all of those decisions.
Trust me, they know it's
not good to operate this way.
They will give us orders soon, huh?
You're right. Cat's in charge.
Everything will be fine.
I'm sorry. I feel like a fool.
You just ran out of patience.
But don't worry.
You're doing a good job.
That's why
Mr. Radcliff gave
you those sugar apples.
How is that going, by the way?
Did you finish
your allotment yet?
Yes. Just last night,
I processed four barrels worth.
That means it's time
to start working on your piece.
I wonder which one of us
can make the superior entry.
You're amazing. Keith.
I haven't even had
a chance to think about what
I'm going to make yet.
You have an idea in mind?
Yes. Well.
I do, but. May I ask why
you requested to use
shall as your model?
No. That's simple.
The Royal family tends
to respond well to sugar confections
that feature a fairy motif.
In the kingdom's Head temple, the Church
of Saint Louis and Bell.
There's a book
about their history with
sugar confections.
Do you like it? Lovely.
Yes. Somehow you've captured
Shell's essence perfectly.
His hair,
his eyes and eyelashes. Once
you had all those details,
it'll be exquisite.
This piece is nothing
short of breathtaking.
Oh. It makes me happy
to hear you say that.
If I had made this,
could I have done that while?
Now that I've seen
what he can do.
Is there anything I could
make that would.
Huh? Is that shell?
And there's Miss Bridget.
I am sorry to call you
out here so unexpectedly.
I'm confused.
Do you really not belong
to that Anne girl?
I made a grave mistake.
It's fine. Forget it.
Wait. Listen.
The truth is.
My fiancé was chosen
for me by my family.
I didn't love him, but I didn't
even understand love yet,
so I didn't
mind in the beginning.
But the other day
when I saw you,
my heart was racing so fast
I couldn't bear it.
I think I love you.
I know that I do.
What's the trouble, then?
Oh, it's nothing at all.
We should go now.
It's pretty late.
We should be getting
back to work. Stop that.
But if you truly
don't belong to her,
then you have the freedom
to do as you please, right?
And so what if I do? You think
I would kiss you if I were
a human and not a fairy? Would
that change your tactic? What?
Why were shallow Miss
Bridget acting so close?
Would you have done
the same if you were trying
to seduce Keith Powell
or Alf Hingley instead?
I don't suppose so.
I would be too ashamed.
But since I'm a fairy, it doesn't
embarrass you, is that it?
Huh? It's no different than buying a
companion fairy at the market.
It isn't like that.
If it is love you want,
then you'll have to steal
my wing and command it of me.
There's something wrong. An.
Oh, no, I'm all right.
Huh? Let's go. Run with me!
Wait!
Uh,
goodness. What was that about?
It's time to start work.
And running is a quick
way to put
your problems behind you.
But I'll always be here
to listen if you want to talk.
For now, focus on
making something amazing
and competing against me.
All right. Sure. Mm.